Guide to the Eric Moe Collection, 1976- UA.90.F96
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- I Want a Boyfriend with Antlers, 2011 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Drafts. Computer-generated score., 4.
    a. Undated. pp. 1-3. Text underlay. b. Undated. pp. 1-3. Text underlay. c. Undated. pp. 1-3. Text underlay. d. Undated. pp. 3-5. Some text underlay. Additions/corrections in pencil. e. Dated 1/27. pp. 1-3. Additions/corrections in pencil. f. Dated 1/30. pp. 1-6. Text underlay. Additions/corrections in pencil. g. Dated 1/31. pp. 1-8. Text underlay. Additions/corrections in pencil. h. Dated 2/2. pp. 4-8. Text underlay. Additions/corrections in pencil.
- Meanwhile Back at the Ranch, 2011 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  Instrumentation: Flute, Clarinet in B-flat, Violin, Viola, Cello, Percussion, Piano.
  Commission: Made possible by a grant from the Jebediah Foundation New Music Commissions.
  - Handwritten sheet in pencil with ideas for changes in the work., 1.
  - Sketches. Manuscript. [52] leaves., 2.
  - Drafts. Computer-generated full scores., 3.
    a. Dated 1/27. 109 pages. b. Dated 2/28. 39 pages (incomplete).
  - Drafts. Computer-generated reduced scores., 4.
    a. Dated 12/4/10. 17 pages. b. Dated 12/4/10. 30 pages. Subtitle on caption: Fresh crispy tone poems #2.
- Of Color Braided All Desire, 2011 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  Instrumentation: 2 Versions. 1. Soprano, Piano. 2. Soprano, String Quartet (2 violins, viola, cello).
  Dedication: For Christine Brandes and the Brentano String Quartet.
  Commission: South Mountain Concerts, Pittsfield, MA.
  Note: Text by May Swenson. Contents. I. Swimmers. II. Four Word Lines. III. Fireflies. IV. Incantation.
  - Texts typewritten, with composer's analysis and potential compositional rendering. [4] leaves., 1.
  - Sketches. Manuscript. Various foldings., 2.
  - Computer-generated scores., 3.
    a. Voice, Piano. 44 pages. b. Voice, Piano. 26 pages. c. Voice, String Quartet. 33 pages. d. Voice, String Quartet. 33 pages. On caption: "reh letters/vocal dynamics" in pencil. e. Voice, String Quartet. 34 pages. Dated 11/9. On caption: "reh letters/vocal dynamics" in pink pencil.
  - Computer-generated parts. Violin I. pp. 1-6, 8-13., 4.
  - Drafts. Computer-generated., 5.
    a. Voice, Piano. Dated 6/2/11-1/2/12 and Undated. b. Voice, String Quartet. Dated 6/20/11-1/19/12 and Undated.
- Rapid Transit, 2011 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  Note: Text by William Carlos Williams.
  - Texts typewritten, with composer's analysis and potential compositional rendering. [4] leaves., 1.
  - Sketches. Manuscript. 2 leaves., 2.
  - Computer-generated score. 12 pages. Printed on gray paper., 3.
  - Computer-generated score. 12 pages. Printed on gray paper. "Restless" written in pencil after initial tempo marking., 4.
  - Computer-generated score. 12 pages. Printed on gray paper. Dated 10/13. Corrections in pencil., 5.
  - Computer-generated score. 12 pages. Printed on gray paper. Undated., 6.
  - Drafts. Computer-generated scores., 7.
    a. Undated. 12 pages. No text underlay. Corrections/additions in pencil. b. Undated. 8 pages. No text underlay. Corrections/additions in pencil.
- Tender Nuts to the Tea Towel, 2011 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  Instrumentation: Flute, Bass clarinet, Violin, Cello, Piano.
  Commission: Hoff-Barthelson School.
  Note: Composed during a residency at the Carmargo Foundation, Cassis, France.
  - Sketches. Manuscript. [11] leaves., 1.
  - Computer-generated score. 16 pages. Includes performance and program notes., 2.
  - Drafts. Reduced score. Computer-generated., 3.
    a. Dated 2/2. 6 pages. b. Dated 2/2. pp. 1-2. Title on caption: Calypso. c. Dated 1/27. pp. 1-5. d. Dated 2/1. pp. 4-8. e. Undated. pp. 1-4. f. Undated. pp. 1-5.
  - Drafts. Full score. Computer-generated., 4.
    a. Dated 2/14. 16 pages. Corrections/additions in pencil.
- Valkyrie Suite, 2012 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  Instrumentation: Opera in 1 act.
  Dedication: For Rob Frankenberry.
  Note: Libretto by Rob Handel. Premiered by the Opera Theater of Pittsburgh, Summerfest, July 6, 2012, Hillman Center for the Performing Arts.
  - Full score. Computer-generated. 66 pages., 1.
  - Full score. Computer-generated. 64 pages. Dated 5/25., 2.
  - Full score. Computer-generated. 82 pages., 3.
  - Parts. Computer-generated., 4.
    a. Flute. pp. 1-8 (incomplete). b. Clarinet in B-flat. pp. 8-9 (incomplete). c. Violin. pp. 1-6. d. Cello. pp. 1-11. e. Marimba. pp. 1-7. f. Piano. pp. 1-15.
  - Sketches. Manuscript. 5 bifolios., 5.
  - Vocal scores. Computer-generated., 6.
    a. Undated. pp. [1]-21 (incomplete). b. Undated. pp. [1]-34 (complete). c. Dated 4/21-4/23. pp. [1]-14 (incomplete). d. dated 4/26-4/28. pp. [1]-23 (complete).
  - Libretto. Typescript., 7.
    a. Clean. pp. 1-4. b. With composer's annotations. pp. 1-4.
  - E-mail correspondence, April 11, 2012; 8.
    a. To Robert Frankenberry concerning vocal assignments.